<testimonials>
  <adult>
    <p>A great way to manage your health, increase confidence and relieve stress!</p>
    ~David</adult>
  <adult>
    <p>Karate is a lifelong sport - it is never too late to start.</p>
    ~Mike Collins</adult>
  <adult>
    <p>I found the Tai Chi class to be extremely helpful in centering and focusing my thoughts and breathing.</p>
    <p>I always look forward to it, as joining with you and the class in my practice of Tai Chi always retools my daily practice of Qi Gong breathing and exercise.</p>
    ~Pat</adult>
  <adult>
    <p>Tai Chi has reduced the stress on my lower back and given me greater balance--not just physically but mentally!  Many of the exercises fit into my busy day so easily and allow me to recharge anytime!</p>
    ~Karen ,Natick MA</adult>
  <adult>
    <p>I’ve been taking T’ai Chi classes for the past 6 years.  I started when I was recovering from a serious knee injury and needed to improve my physical balance.  What I have found is that T’ai Chi has brought both physical and mental balance to my life!  The practice is always energizing; in difficult times it is also healing and renewing.  I can’t recommend it highly enough as a way to de-stress and maintain flexibility.</p>
    ~Patricia Lane , Framingham MA</adult>
  <adult>
    <p>Tai chi has provided me with a sense of  balance, an awareness  and appreciation of the connection between mind, body and  spirit and an over-all sense of well-being.  The meditation segment  leaves me feeling positive and centered.  The chi kung exercises supply energy and flexibility in a gentle way.  And it is fun!  What better way to nurture yourself?</p>
    ~Kit Segarra ,Framingham MA</adult>
  <adult>
    <p>To me, the Tai Chi class is a chance to work with excellent instructors and congenial fellow students to benefit both mind and body. 
      We learn and practice techniques that can improve our health and help bring balance to our lives, and we are reminded and encouraged to use those techniques throughout our day.</p>
    ~Dave, Natick MA</adult>
</testimonials>
