<testimonials>
  <kids>
    <p>"Karate Rocks!" That is what my son says after every class.  He enjoys going to class and showing off all the new things he learns.  Thank you for everything so happy we found you and decided to sign him up.  :)</p>
    ~Lucy</kids>
  <kids>
    <p>In 2009 I signed my then seven-year-old daughter up for classes.  She has some special needs.  Mark and the instructors have been nothing but great with her.  They have included her in all activities, modifing where needed to address her medical issues, and have integrated her seamlessly with the other students.  Her balance, strength, coordination and most importantly her self-confidence are light-years ahead of where they were when she started.</p>
    <p>In fact, she convinced me to start with her, and it has been great for me.  I'm now thirty pounds lighter when I started, I've made a fantastic group of friends, and I have lots of opportunities to give back to the community through the studio.  It's been such a positive part of my life.</p>
    ~Ben Jackson</kids>
  <kids>
    <p>Villari's has had a tremendous positive impact on my son. I highly recommend them</p>
    ~Karen</kids>
  <kids>
    <p>When my son first asked to take karate in first grade, I thought it was a horrible idea.  I didn't think he had the focus or self-control to stick with it.  Somehow, the teachers worked magic with him.   He is now in the  fourth grade and a 3rd degree brown belt.  He is on the leadership and demo teams.  He spends over 3 hours a week at Villaris and never misses a class or complains about going.    As he has progressed through the belts, I have seen  tremendous improvement in his self-confidence, self-control and focus.</p>
    ~Sally</kids>
  <kids>
    <p>We originally signed up for karate to help my son with his self-control.  In addition to improving his self-control, he has gained confidence and focus. 
      From movie nights to the Halloween dojo to collecting goods for local agencies, Villaris is a true community. They not only teach karate but also social skills and citizenship.</p>
    ~Lucia</kids>
  <kids>
    <p>"Villari's in Natick has been a wonderful place for my son to grow up. He started lessons at four and loved them. We love the environment, too, so it's been easy to make karate lessons a regular part of our life for the past five years. Mark and the other teachers are just the kind of role models we want for our son."</p>
    ~Le Ann</kids>
</testimonials>
